Finding aid to the Mary Daly papers SSC.MS.00637
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. Personal, 1950-2010; 10.626 linear feet (14 containers)
  - "Anna...", 2004-2010 (Box 61)
  - "Anna..." Translation Version floppy disk, 2010
  - Sally Roesch Wagner Election Thoughts, 2006 (Box 61)
  - Amy Goodman- Democracy Now, 2007 (Box 61)
  - Sinister Wisdom, 2007 (Box 61)
  - Dr Sabrina Popp, MD, 2003 (Box 61)
  - Poindexter, etc Tenor, 2003 (Box 61)
  - Articles for Extinction of Species New Research, 2004 (Box 61)
  - Personal, 2002-2006 (Box 61)
  - Whittier/Gage Foundation, 2005 (Box 61)
  - Virginia Woolf's Anon. (Box 61)
  - The War Against Women Bush NY Times, 2003 (Box 61)
  - Iraq- Bio-Engineered Foods, 2005 (Box 61)
  - Amish School Killings Clippings, 2006 (Box 61)
  - Vermont Women Killed, 2006 (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 61)
  - US Government Gold Coin, 2004 (Box 61)
  - Extinction Articles, 2004 (Box 61)
  - Dworkin Obituary by Mary in The Phoenix, 2005 (Box 61)
  - Judith Rutuly and Barbara Ehrenreich, 2004 (Box 61)
  - Matilda Joselyn Gage Foundation, 2004 (Box 61)
  - Computer Instructions (Box 61)
  - Cards (personal), 1987-1988 (Box 61)
  - HDS, 2002 (Box 61)
  - Women and Drugs, 2003 (Box 61)
  - Current Mass Extinction and 6th Extinction by Richard Leakey, 2004 (Box 61)
  - AAR, 2002 (Box 61)
  - Bill Joy, 2004 (Box 61)
  - Northampton Protest, 1989 (Box 61)
  - Big Dan's Rape Trial, 1984 (Box 61)
  - Robin Benedict Murder, 1984 (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1993-2006 (Box 61)
  - Animal Photos, 2008 (Box 61)
  - Jen's Immediate To Do File, 2006-2007 (Box 61)
  - Rainbow Vision Santa Fe, 2007 (Box 61)
  - Gore Vidal, Amy Goodman on Bush, 2006-2008 (Box 61)
  - Newsweek: Race for Survival, 2008 (Box 61)
  - Computer, 2007 (Box 61)
  - Gerda Weiler matriarchalen, 2007 (Box 61)
  - Computer Notes, 2006 (Box 61)
  - From Office Desktop (Box 61)
  - Physical Therapy, 2003 (Box 61)
  - Gregory Solgado, 2002 (Box 61)
  - Electromagnetic Radiation Dangers, 2000-2004 (Box 61)
  - Carla Elland, 2002 (Box 61)
  - Urgent (Gorillas and Chimpanzees) (Box 61)
  - Causes- To Pay, 2004 (Box 61)
  - NRDC, 2004 (Box 61)
  - Wall of Tolerance, 2002 (Box 61)
  - Grey2K, 2003 (Box 61)
  - Causes (Box 61)
  - Hightower Lowdoun Newspaper, 2002 (Box 61)
  - Hormone Replacement Therapy, 2003 (Box 61)
  - The Wilderness Society (Box 61)
  - Evelyn Embry (Cat Woman), 2002 (Box 61)
  - Canned Hunt, 2003 (Box 61)
  - Seals, 2003 (Box 61)
  - War on Women/Abortion (Box 61)
  - Female Genital Mutilation, 2003 (Box 61)
  - Reject the War, 2006 (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous Feminist Magazines, 1975-2001 (Box 62)
  - Jane Caputi, 2004 (Box 62)
  - Boston Police- Stolen Wallet, 2006 (Box 62)
  - Robert Kavanagh/Computer Help, 2006 (Box 62)
  - Neanderthals and Modern Humans (Box 62)
  - Capitalism, 2003 (Box 62)
  - Consciousness, 2000 (Box 62)
  - Disappearing Women, 2003 (Box 62)
  - Women/Feminism/Stepford, 2003 (Box 62)
  - Routledge- Publishers, 2004 (Box 62)
  - Hotwire, 1994 (Box 62)
  - Women's Publications, 1984-2002 (Box 62)
  - The Women's Museum, 2000 (Box 62)
  - St Pedophilia Cartoon (Box 62)
  - Arbella Mutual Insurance Company, 2004 (Box 62)
  - Spinal Stenosis, 2008 (Box 62)
  - AI Film Reviews, 2001 (Box 62)
  - Disappearing Males, 2003 (Box 62)
  - Right Wing Organizations, 2003 (Box 62)
  - Mandala- Vicki Noble, 2001 (Box 62)
  - Carol Conway in Ashcroft (Box 62)
  - NWSA on BC cash and Mary Daly, 2000 (Box 62)
  - Stem Cell Research, 2001-2002 (Box 62)
  - GM Humans already created, 2001 (Box 62)
  - Goddessing, 1997-1998 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings Ireland, 1997 (Box 62)
  - Wild Cat (Box 62)
  - National Writers Union, 1997 (Box 62)
  - Veteran Feminists of America, 1994-1997 (Box 62)
  - Magnetism (Box 62)
  - Tree Marriage, Roots, 1995 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous Loose Documents, 2002-2003 (Box 62)
  - Nixon and Arbella- Automobile Insurance, 2002 (Box 62)
  - I Book, 2000-2001 (Box 62)
  - Death Threat, 2000 (Box 62)
  - PRA, 2000-2001 (Box 62)
  - WILPF, 2000 (Box 62)
  - World Watch (Box 62)
  - MultiPure (Box 62)
  - Business- Tapes, 1998-1999 (Box 62)
  - Iraq, 2003 (Box 62)
  - Greyhound Racing, 2000 (Box 62)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt, 2000 (Box 62)
  - Democracy Now Matt Taibbi- "Worst Congress Ever", 2006 (Box 62)
  - Laura Flanders- Anti-Feminist Women, 1999 (Box 62)
  - Sally Rosch Wagner, 2005-2006 (Box 62)
  - Gage Foundation- Sally R. Wagner, 2008 (Box 62)
  - Gage Foundation Website, 2004-2005 (Box 62)
  - Starhawk, 2000 (Box 62)
  - Appliances, 2005-2006 (Box 62)
  - Amy Goodman, 2008 (Box 62)
  - The Fifth Cause- Exemplar, 2005 (Box 62)
  - Guantanamo Bay/Abu Ghraib, 2004 (Box 62)
  - Catholic Church- Abuse Scandal, 2004 (Box 62)
  - Collapse of Patriarchy, 2004 (Box 62)
  - Storage Bin, 2006 (Box 62)
  - NCPSSM, 2006 (Box 62)
  - TIAA CREF, 2006 (Box 62)
  - Bills- Not Paid, 2006 (Box 62)
  - Verizon, 2005-2006 (Box 62)
  - Personal- cards and letters, 1985-2006 (Box 62)
  - NSTAR, 2007 (Box 62)
  - Physical Therapy, 2006 (Box 62)
  - Crotch Doctor, 2006 (Box 62)
  - Iraq- Women, Other Articles, Info, 2003 (Box 62)
  - Peacework Magazine, 1974-1979 (Box 62)
  - Gene Watch, 2000-2001 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous Magazines, 1998-1999 (Box 62)
  - Gene Watch, 1994-1999 (Box 62)
  - Feminist Bookstore News/Catalog, 1996-1997 (Box 63)
  - Goddessing, 1997-1999 (Box 63)
  - Cat Photos, 1983-1991 (Box 63)
  - Code Pink, 2003 (Box 63)
  - Grandmother Kate (Box 63)
  - Photograph with Axe, 1998 (Box 63)
  - Joann stuff, 1979 (Box 63)
  - World Can't Wait, 2006 (Box 63)
  - O'Dalaigh History (Ireland) (Box 63)
  - Afghanistan, 2001 (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001-2005 (Box 63)
  - Patriot Act/Iraq/Fascism, 2004-2005 (Box 63)
  - John Stolt, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Environment (Box 63)
  - Media Censorship by U.S. Corporations, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Rental Agreements, 1978-1982 (Box 63)
  - House Lore- History, 1982 (Box 63)
  - Mortgage House Reciepts, 1984 (Box 63)
  - North Leverette Road Architecture Plans (Box 63)
  - Leverett House Bills and Reciepts, 1981-1982 (Box 63)
  - Leverett expenses, 1984 (Box 63)
  - Lab Reports on Air, 1983-1987 (Box 63)
  - Leverett House Will, 1982 (Box 63)
  - House II Insurance, 1979-1985 (Box 63)
  - Leverett Leases, 1984-1986 (Box 63)
  - Tax and Purchase, 1979 (Box 63)
  - Receipts, 1981 (Box 63)
  - First National Joint Account, 1982-1983 (Box 63)
  - Sale of Leverett House, 1984 (Box 63)
  - Cathy Bickford and D.H. Jones, 1984 (Box 63)
  - Leverett House Expenses, 1985 (Box 63)
  - Leverett House Sale, 1985 (Box 63)
  - Leverett House Expenses, 1985 (Box 63)
  - House, 1983 (Box 63)
  - Leverett Urea Formaldehyde, 1976-1986 (Box 63)
  - Smith College Re: donating papers to the Collection @ Smith, 2006 (Box 63)
  - $300 Tax Rebate, 2001 (Box 63)
  - Diary, 1984 (Box 63)
  - Millennium Ecosystem Assessment, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Feminist Majority Ellie Smeal (Box 63)
  - Global Warming- Al Gore, 2006 (Box 63)
  - New Yorker on Global Warming, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Human Rights Sudan (Box 63)
  - NRDC (Box 63)
  - Opus Dei (Ugh), 2006 (Box 63)
  - Center for New Words, 2006 (Box 63)
  - Code Pink for Peace Boston (Box 63)
  - Receipts of Donations, 2007 (Box 63)
  - MJ Gage, 2004 (Box 63)
  - Jack Burke, 2001-2004 (Box 63)
  - Religious Right, 2006 (Box 63)
  - Angie Murillo (Box 63)
  - Smith College- Mary Daly Papers, 2002-2003 (Box 63)
  - Laura Diamond, 2000-2001 (Box 63)
  - IRS, 2008 (Box 63)
  - Fundamentalism, 2007 (Box 63)
  - Congo/rapes/news articles, 2005-2007 (Box 63)
  - Robin Morgan- Goodbye to All Part II, 2008 (Box 63)
  - Helen Caddes (Box 63)
  - Columbus- Doctrine of Discovery, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Footbinding Article, 2003 (Box 63)
  - Addresses, Notes, 2005-2007 (Box 63)
  - Quotes- Gage (Box 63)
  - Read- To Be Read, 2007 (Box 63)
  - Courts Strip Elders- Boston Globe, 2008 (Box 63)
  - Aztecs- June Nash (Box 63)
  - Harriet Ellenberger Global Dimming, 2007 (Box 63)
  - Iraq, 2008 (Box 63)
  - Gage Publications, 2004-2005 (Box 63)
  - Gage Foundation, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Off Our Backs- Hullabaloo, 2008 (Box 63)
  - Feminist Majority (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous no action taken, 2007 (Box 63)
  - Plumbing- Bob Lee pd, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Frances Newton Executed, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Freida Jacques American Indians and Other Atrocities, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Congo Genocide (Box 63)
  - Medicare/BC, 2003-2007 (Box 63)
  - Computers, 1993 (Box 63)
  - Seeds, 2003 (Box 63)
  - Hedge School Research, 2007 (Box 63)
  - Birth Certificate, 1928 (Box 63)
  - The G.W. Bush Gang and I.B. Farben, 2001 (Box 64)
  - Turning Pt Project NY Times Ads- Econ etc, 2000 (Box 64)
  - French Journalists Book Exposing 911 as Right Wing US Plot, 2002 (Box 64)
  - US Supreme Court Lies, 2000 (Box 64)
  - Bush's Team and GM Food- Bush's Corporate Cabinet, 2001 (Box 64)
  - Bush and Right Wing Stealth Tactics, 2001 (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, 2006 (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, 2004-2009 (Box 64)
  - GW Bush- Nazis Cabinet, 2001 (Box 64)
  - Dear Mama by Eileen Pagan, 1979 (Box 64)
  - Center for New Words, 2003 (Box 64)
  - Global Dimming, 2004 (Box 64)
  - "The Term Matriarch" by Heide Goettner-Abendroth, 2004 (Box 64)
  - Global Warming- Tsunamis, 2004-2005 (Box 64)
  - Daly's Death, 2010 (Box 64)
  - Photos, 1996 (Box 64)
  - College Entrance Diploma, 1946 (Box 64)
  - BA Diploma, 1950 (Box 64)
  - Academic Degrees, 1942-1950 (Box 64)
  - Anna Daly Funeral Book (Box 64)
  - Notebook- Ireland Trip (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 64)
  - Birthday Book from Coyote Mom Meadow, 2007 (Box 64)
  - High School Yearbook, 1950 (Box 64)
  - Will, 2009 (Box 64)
  - Fribourg Documents, 1952-1965 (Box 64)
  - Will, 1974 (Box 64)
  - Will, Dur. Power of Attorney, DPA Literary, Health Care Proxy, 2006 (Box 64)
  - Internet Connection Verizon (Box 64)
  - Bank of America- Trevor Spaulding, 2008 (Box 64)
  - Social Security, 2005 (Box 64)
  - Taxes, 2007 (Box 64)
  - TIAA CREF, 2003-2007 (Box 64)
  - Minimum Distribution TIAA CREF, 2002-2005 (Box 64)
  - Taxes, 1997-2005 (Box 64)
  - Memo Book (Box 65)
  - Stationary (Box 65)
  - Daly Genealogy (Box 65)
  - Mary Daly Photos by Diana Jo Davies (Box 65)
  - Unknown Logo (Box 65)
  - High School Diploma, 1946 (Box 65)
  - Photographs, 1900-1998 (Box 65)
  - Family Photos, 1900-1991 (Box 65)
  - Already Scanned- photos, 1880-2006 (Box 65)
  - Pictures, 1970 (Box 65)
  - Mary Daly Photographs and Some Friends, 1970-1980 (Box 65)
  - Photos- speaking engagements, 1991-2007 (Box 66)
  - Catholic University of America Commencement, 1952 (Box 66)
  - Anna C. Daly, mother, 1923-1969 (Box 66)
  - Obituaries, 2010 (Box 66)
  - Matilda Joslyn Gage, 2004 (Box 66)
  - Photo Album- cat (Box 66)
  - Passports and Medical Proxy, 1973-2005 (Box 66)
  - Pd Bills- Misc., 1979-1988 (Box 66)
  - PACE Rainbow Flag, 2002 (Box 67)
  - Postcard Collection (Box 67)
  - Wallet with High School Photos of Daly, possibly belonged to her parents? (Box 67)
  - Tiger Iron-On Patch (Box 67)
  - Mary Daly Ceramic Mug, 1979 (Box 67)
    This handmade mug is decorated with a relief of "Mary Daly", an axe, and a shoe with wings. On the bottom it is signed "S '79."
  - Erin Snow Painting for Daly, 1995 (Box 73)
  - X-Rays of Daly, 1993 (Box 73)
  - Sudie Rakusin Lunar Art Calendars, 1995 (Box 73)
  - Portrait of Daly/family member?, 1929 (Box 73)
  - Women Who Dare Calendars, 1995 (Box 73)
  - The Lunar Calendar, 1979-1980 (Box 73)
  - Heart and Soul Poster, 3 (Box 73)
  - Working Women Unite Poster, 3 (Box 73)
  - Sinister Wisdom Poster, 3 (Box 73)
  - Mary Daly Poster, 3 (Box 73)
  - Panhandling Papers Posters by Kady (Box 73)
  - Photo Collage (Box 73)
  - Women March to Take Back the Night Poster, 1979 (Box 73)
  - Sketch of Daly with Ax, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Video recording of West African percussion demonstration (Station Fox 29, Karem) (Box 74)
  - Video recording of a women's group doing readings (deteriorating B&W), 1 items (1 videocassette) (Box 74)
  - Video recording of Roseanne Barr on Entertainment Tonight, 1 items (1 videocassette) (Box 74)
  - Video recording of Mary Daly, 2012-11-25; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 74)
  - Video recording of Daly Memorial, 2010-05-01; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 74)
  - Floppy disk of "Anna" translation, 2010-04-06; 1 items (1 floppy disk) (Box 74)
  - Floppy disk of saved documents from January 28th, 1 items (1 floppy disk) (Box 74)
  - Floppy disk of "Wendy", 1993-09-03; 2 items (2 floppy disk) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Ella Tante (initially exercise warm-up tunes?), 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Gladys, 1975; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recordings of meditation/relaxation techniques, 4 items (4 audiocassettes) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Peggy Huddleston meditation, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Jennifer Abod (WXPN, Mediawise) interviews - crew, Billy Jean King, Ted Turner, 1981-05-23; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Martha Copeland and others (music?) (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of "How to Change a Flat Tire" - traditional music of Ireland and Scotland (Box 74)
  - Ich träume weiblich (I dream female) - Barbara Starrett, 1978 (Box 71)
  - Die getrennten Schwestern (The separated sisters: women after the Council) - Gertrud Heinselmann, 1967 (Box 71)
  - Like There's No Tomorrow: Meditations for Women Leaving Patriarchy - Carolyn Gage, 1997 (Box 71)
  - Lesbian Studies: Present and Future - Ed. Margaret Cruikshank, 1982 (Box 71)
  - Biblioteca Femina: A herstory of book collections concerning women - Maryann Turner, 1978 (Box 71)
  - De Kunst van het Kaaien (The art of the [Key?]: Myth and reality in the book Gyn/Ecology by Mary Daly) - Irmgard Maria Busch, 1985 (Box 71)
  - The Reflowering of the Goddess - Gloria Feman Orenstein, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Ancient Greece - Ruth Adamson, 1988 (Box 71)
  - Traces of Misogyny in Women's Schooling - Meredith Elizabeth Horning Reiniger-Shapiro, 1982 (Box 71)
  - Sinister Wisdom 43/44: The 15th Anniversary Retrospective, 1991 (Box 71)
  - The Double Goddess: Women Sharing Power - Vicki Noble, 2003 (Box 71)
  - Word Controlled Humans - John Harland, 1981 (Box 71)
  - Heresies # 15: "Racism is the Issue", 1982 (Box 72)
  - Foreign Feminist Publications, 1974-1979 (Box 72)
  - Feminist Magazines, 1971-1976 (Box 72)
  - Genesis:The Magazine of the College of Saint Rose: "Saint Rose in New York", 2004 (Box 72)
  - Matriarchy and the Mountains 3: Convention Proceedings, Ed. Michela Zucca, 1999-2000 (Box 72)
  - Finding Grandmama God (and Talking Things Over with Her) - Mary Feagan, 1992 (Box 72)
  - Off Our Backs Vol. 34, Nos. 9 and 10: "Men Can Stop Rape...", 2004 (Box 72)
  - ReVision Vol. 25 No. 1: "Fierce Goddesses, Great Mothers, and Yoginis: The Archaeomythology of Devotion", 2002 (Box 72)
  - Symphoros No. 1: "De Reis is Thuis (The journey is at home), 1988 (Box 72)
  - La Vie En Rose No. 19, 1984 (Box 72)
  - The Second Coming of Joan of Arc - Carolyn Gage, 1987 (Box 72)
  - Maize #84, 2007-2008 (Box 72)
  - Social Policy Vol. 4 No. 3, 1973 (Box 72)
  - Laughing (UGBC Women's Issues Lit. Mag): "Medusa", 1993 (Box 72)
  - Ideas of Today Vol. 22 No. 3, 1975 (Box 72)
  - Womb With Views: A Contradictionary of the English Language - Kate Musgrave, 1986 (Box 72)
  - The Double Goddess: Women Sharing Power - Vicki Noble, 2000 (Box 72)
  - Notes From The Second Year: "Women's Liberation: Major Writings of the Radical Feminist", 1970 (Box 72)
  - Liquid Lovers - Sandra J. Taylor, Esther K. Heggie, 1989 (Box 72)
  - The Black Scholar Vol. 13 Nos. 4 and 5: "The Best of the Black Scholar: The Black Woman", 1982 (Box 72)
  - Women's Studies International Forum Vol. 11 No. 4, 1988 (Box 72)
  - Women Who Defied Prejudice - C. H. Gibbs-Smith, 1956 (Box 72)
  - Woman of Power No. 23: "Sacred Spaces", 1994 (Box 72)
  - Maenad (women's lit journal) Vol. 1 No. 1, 1980 (Box 72)
  - Maenad Vol. 2 No. 1, 1981 (Box 72)
  - Maenad Vol. 1 No. 3, 1981 (Box 72)
  - WomENergy: A Woman's Guide to Boston College, 1978-1979 (Box 72)
  - The Dangers of the Hour - 1890 speech by Matilda Joslyn Gage, 2004 (Box 72)
  - Queer Culture: Our History and Our Legacy - Julie R. Enzer, 2006 (Box 72)
  - My Lesbian Herstory - Jolie R. Enszer (Box 72)
  - HLLQ (Harrington Lesbian Literary Quarterly) Vol. 7 No. 3, 2006 (Box 72)
  - Witches, Midwive and Nurses: A History of Women Healers - Barbara Ehrenreich, Deirdre English (Box 72)
  - The Feminist English Dictionary Vol. 1: "An Intelligent Woman's Guide to Dirty Words", 1973 (Box 72)
  - Sinister Wisdom (lesbian lit mag) #13, 1980 (Box 72)
  - Sinister Wisdom #14, 1980 (Box 72)
  - Trivia, 1982 (Box 72)
  - Sinister Wisdom #72: "Utopia", 2007-2008 (Box 72)
  - Sinister Wisdom #70: 30th Anniversary, 2007 (Box 72)
  - Sinister Wisdom #19, 1982 (Box 72)
  - Amazon Quarterly Vol. 3 No. 1, 1974 (Box 72)
  - Lesbian Ethics Vol. 4 No. 1, 1990 (Box 72)
  - Matilda Joslyn Gage: She Who Holds The Sky - Sally Roesch Wagner, 1998 (Box 72)
  - Quest Vol. 3 No.: "Communication and Control", 1976 (Box 72)
  - Asking No Man Pardon: The Philosophical Significance of Being Lesbian - Elsa Gidlow, 1975 (Box 72)
  - Womb with Views: A Contradictionary of the Enguish Language - Kate Musgrave, 1989 (Box 72)
  - Sisters in Spirit: Haudenosaunee (Iroquois) Influence on Early American Feminists - Sally Roesch Wagner, 2001 (Box 72)
  - Language and Woman's Place - Robin Lakoff, 1975 (Box 72)
  - The Death-defying Dance - Pauline Isabel, 1984 (Box 72)
  - Lesbiana and Women in Literature (Elysian Fields stock catalog) (Box 72)
  - Shedding Grace (and other stories) - Mab Maher (Box 72)
  - Peace and Power: A Handbook of Feminist Process - Charlene Eldrige Wheeler, Peggy L. Chinn, 1984 (Box 72)
  - Yellow Ribbons - Ruth Adamson, 1983 (Box 72)
  - Serpent (W)rite - Betsy Warland, 1987 (Box 72)
  - Women's Worlds: Visions and Revisions - Program from the Third International Interdisciplinary Congress on Women, 1987 (Box 72)
  - L'émergence d'une Culture au Féminin (The emergence of a feminine culture) - Ed. Marisa Zavalloni, 1987 (Box 72)
  - Le Féminisme ou la mort. (Feminism or death.) - Françoise d´Eaubonne, 1974 (Box 72)
  - The Dreaded Comparison: Human and Animal Slavery - Marjorie Spiegel, 1988 (Box 72)
  - The Yellow Wallpaper - Charlotte Perkins Gilman, 1973 (Box 72)
  - Scum Manifesto - Valerie Solanas, 1983 (Box 72)
  - Woman at Point Zero - Nawal El Saadawi (trans. from Arabic by Sherif Hetata), 1983 (Box 72)
  - Lust en Gratie (Lust and Grace, Dutch lesbian culture mag) #7 - contains essay about the other/world/journey in Daly's work, 1985 (Box 72)
  - International Feminism: Networking Against Female Sexual Slavery - Eds. Kathleen Barry, Charlotte Bunch, Shirley Castley, 1983 (Box 72)
  - Monster - Robin Morgan, 1972 (Box 72)
  - Daughters of Copper Woman - Anne Cameron, 1981 (Box 72)
  - The Feminist Press Catalog No. 1: "Elizabeth Cady Stanton" by Mary Ann B. Oakley, 1972 (Box 72)
  - Scum Manifesto - Valerie Solanas, 1996 (Box 72)
  - Quest Vol. 1 No. 4: "Women and Spirituality", 1975 (Box 72)
  - Complaints and Disorders: The Sexual Politics of Sickness - Barbara Ehrenreich and Deirdre English, 1973 (Box 72)
  - Leader's Guide to A Journey is Home, a film about Nelle Morton, 1989 (Box 72)
  - Woedende Woorden Woorden Van Hoop (Angry Words of Hope: the development in Mary Daly's thinking) - Maaike de Haardt, 1985 (Box 72)
  - She Said He Said: An annotated bibliography of sex differences in language, speech and non-verbal communication - Ed. Nancy Henley, Barrie Thorne, 1975 (Box 72)
  - Colei che dà la vita colei che dà la forma (She who gives life, she who gives form) - Luciana Percovich, 2009 (Box 72)
  - Against Sadomasochism: A radical feminist analysis - Ed. Linden, Pagano, Russell, Star, 1982 (Box 72)
  - Original artwork by friends (Folder 75)